Guide to the H.E Butti Bin Bishr Collection AD.MC.093
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- H.E. Butti Bin Bishr at Sites of Public Works Projects in the United Arab Emirates
  - H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan (left) with two unidentified men., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000034_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Officials; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; United Arab Emirates; Political Leadership; Hamdan bin Mohammed Al Nayhan, Sheikh, c.1930s-1989
  - Four men talking with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle) about his public works projects outside the Abu Dhabi Telegraph and Telephone Company., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000035_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Construction; Facial Hair
  - Two men talking with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) about his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000036_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 17.7 x 12.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Men; United Arab Emirates; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Officials
  - Three men interviewing H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) about his public works projects outside the Abu Dhabi Telegraph and Telephone Company., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000037_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Microphones; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Cigarettes; Smoking
  - A crowd on site of a public housing project., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000038_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Buildings; Construction; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates; Crowds
  - Two men shake hands in an office, with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle) in the background., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000039_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Men; Group Portraits; Offices; Furnishings; Paintings; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Pens/Inkwells; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Officials
  - Two men talking with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle) about his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000040_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 17.7 x 12.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; United Arab Emirates; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Canes/Walking Sticks; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr on site of one of his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000041_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 17.7 x 12.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Canes/Walking Sticks; Construction; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Buildings
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) in an office with an unidentified man., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000042_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Offices; Furnishings; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates; Flags; Canes/Walking Sticks; Books
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr standing in the entrance of a trailer, with the flag of Abu Dhabi on its exterior., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000043_000001; Mahmood Beg, M. (United Arab Emirates); 1 Photographic Prints 12.4 x 15 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Flags; Furnishings; Men; Individual Portraits; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates; Pens/Inkwells
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) with two other men on site of one of his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000044_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Construction; United Arab Emirates; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Smoking; Cigarettes
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) talking with an unidentified man looking at a circuit breaker., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000045_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Men; Group Portraits; Electricity; Clocks/Watches; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - Three men talking with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left) about his public works projects outside the Abu Dhabi Telegraph and Telephone Company., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000046_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Buildings; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Electricity; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Officials
  - Men on site of a public housing project., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000047_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Men; Group Portraits; Construction; United Arab Emirates; Clocks/Watches; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair
  - A man talking with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) about one of his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000048_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Safe; Canes/Walking Sticks; Men; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Jewelry; Clocks/Watches
  - A group of men with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (front, middle) about his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000049_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Buildings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Clocks/Watches; Cigarettes; Smoking; Construction
  - Two men interviewing H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) about his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000050_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Canes/Walking Sticks; Group Portraits; Men; Pens/Inkwells; Cigarettes; Smoking; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates
  - Three men talking with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) about his public works projects outside the Abu Dhabi Telegraph and Telephone Company., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000051_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Street Lamps; Officials
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) with three men working on public works project plans in an office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000052_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Offices; Pens/Inkwells; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Clocks/Watches; Officials; United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr on site of one of his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000053_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Buildings; Construction; Clocks/Watches; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair
  - Four men talking with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle) about his public works projects outside the Abu Dhabi Telegraph and Telephone Company., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000054_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Buildings; Signs/Signposts; Flags; Mosques; Streets/Roads; Religious Sites; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Facial Hair; Officials; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Smoking; Cigarette cards
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) speaking to a group of men on site of one of his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000055_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Officials; Construction; United Arab Emirates; Clocks/Watches; Buildings
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr sitting in a chair with his eyes closed., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000056_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Furnishings; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates; Facial Hair
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right, obscured) with two men in an office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000057_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 17.7 x 12.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Offices; Furnishings; Paintings; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Pens/Inkwells; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Clocks/Watches
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right, obscured) with two men in an office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000058_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 17.7 x 12.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Offices; Furnishings; Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; United Arab Emirates; Pens/Inkwells; Clocks/Watches; Officials; Paintings; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan
  - Two men shaking hands in an office, with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr in the background., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000059_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Paintings; Offices; Furnishings; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Clocks/Watches; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; United Arab Emirates; Pens/Inkwells
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr in an office with a bottle of Old Spice., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000060_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Offices; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Officials; Clocks/Watches; United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left) reviewing public works plans in an office with four men., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000061_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Clocks/Watches; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates; Offices; Pens/Inkwells; Officials; Furnishings; Books; Paintings
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) talking with a man about his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000062_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 17.7 x 12.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Safe; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Canes/Walking Sticks; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Clocks/Watches
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) talking with a man about his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000063_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Canes/Walking Sticks; United Arab Emirates; Safe; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials
  - Four men talking with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the right) about his public works projects outside the Abu Dhabi Telegraph and Telephone Company., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000064_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Officials; Construction; Buildings; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Clocks/Watches; Cigarettes; Smoking; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (front, right) leading a tour of a public housing project., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000065_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Group Portraits; Men; Crowds; Streets/Roads; Construction; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Mountains/Hills; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Smoking; Cigarettes; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan (right) talking with four men in his office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000066_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Officials; Offices; Furnishings; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; United Arab Emirates; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches; Drinks/Beverages; Royalty; Political Leadership; Hamdan bin Mohammed Al Nayhan, Sheikh, c.1930s-1989
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and an unidentified man in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000067_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Offices; Furnishings; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; United Arab Emirates; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Political Leadership; Royalty; Hamdan bin Mohammed Al Nayhan, Sheikh, c.1930s-1989
  - Three men talking with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the right) about his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000068_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Officials; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches; Safe
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and four other men reviewing public works plans in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000069_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Offices; Furnishings; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; United Arab Emirates; Pens/Inkwells; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Political Leadership; Royalty; Hamdan bin Mohammed Al Nayhan, Sheikh, c.1930s-1989
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and four other men reviewing public works plans in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000070_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Offices; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; United Arab Emirates; Pens/Inkwells; Books; Jewelry; Officials; Political Leadership; Royalty; Hamdan bin Mohammed Al Nayhan, Sheikh, c.1930s-1989
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and four other men reviewing public works plans in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000071_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Offices; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Pens/Inkwells; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Books; United Arab Emirates; Officials; Clocks/Watches; Political Leadership; Royalty; Hamdan bin Mohammed Al Nayhan, Sheikh, c.1930s-1989
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and four other men reviewing public works plans in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000072_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; United Arab Emirates; Facial Hair; Offices; Officials; Pens/Inkwells; Books; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Furnishings; Political Leadership; Royalty; Hamdan bin Mohammed Al Nayhan, Sheikh, c.1930s-1989
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and four other men reviewing public works plans in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000073_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Offices; Furnishings; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Pens/Inkwells; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Books; Political Leadership; Royalty; Hamdan bin Mohammed Al Nayhan, Sheikh, c.1930s-1989
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and four other men reviewing public works plans in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000074_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Furnishings; Offices; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Pens/Inkwells; Books; Facial Hair; Political Leadership; Royalty; Hamdan bin Mohammed Al Nayhan, Sheikh, c.1930s-1989
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and four other men reviewing public works plans in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000075_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Books; Furnishings; Officials; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Offices; Pens/Inkwells; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; United Arab Emirates; Political Leadership; Royalty; Hamdan bin Mohammed Al Nayhan, Sheikh, c.1930s-1989
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and four other men reviewing public works plans in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000076_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Books; Pens/Inkwells; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Furnishings; Offices; United Arab Emirates; Officials; Political Leadership; Royalty; Hamdan bin Mohammed Al Nayhan, Sheikh, c.1930s-1989
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left) greeting an unidentified man., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000077_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Palm Trees; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Hats
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle) working on a public works project with his team., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000078_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Offices; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates; Books; Clocks/Watches; Pens/Inkwells; Facial Hair
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) talking with a group of people about his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000079_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Buildings; Clocks/Watches; Books; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; United Arab Emirates; Officials
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr sitting in a chair with his eyes closed., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000080_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Offices; Furnishings; United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) talking with a man about his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000081_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Construction; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) being interviewed by three men about his public works projects outside the Abu Dhabi Telegraph and Telephone Company., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000082_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Officials; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Microphones; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches; Smoking; Cigarettes; Cars/Trucks; Transportation
  - An automobile parked outside the Ministry of Labor's office in Ras Al Khaimah., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000083_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cars/Trucks; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Transportation; Offices; Arabic Calligraphy; Signs/Signposts; Electricity
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle, wearing kandoora) with a group of interviewers at one of the public works projects he oversaw., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000084_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Furnishings; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Electricity; Hats; Officials; United Arab Emirates
  - A group of men touring a public housing project., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000085_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair; Clocks/Watches; Cigarettes; United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) talking with a man about his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000086_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)